Romaji Lyric
Romaji Kibun Jojo 	

*Hey DJ kamase
yeah X 3 kibun joujou no
Hari otose oto nara se PAARINAI
Nomo urai X 3 minna de odore!
Hip-Pop PIIPOO
Kakete yo MIRAKURU Number

Yo! Konna jidai ni wakachi au MUSIC
Sagashitakute mawasu chikyuugi
Gura tsuku fuantei seikatsu
Sore dakara BARANSU juushi
Yoi koto bakari ja nai kara “Ganbareru!”
Saiaku na hi ni kikku
Saikidou no botan kurikku!
DJ kakete!! Ima TRIP

Shareteru BIITO ni notte
Kanjiru karada yurasou yo

Hey DJ kamase
yeah X 3 kibun joujou no
Hari otose oto nara se PAARINAI
Nomo urai X 3 minna de odore!
Hip-Pop PIIPOO
Kakete yo MIRAKURU Number

Hip Hop, R&B, Pops Techno, House, Rock...
Hip Pop!!
ORIJINARU sagasu KIIPOINTO
Sorezore no iro kasane awasu REINBOO
Kimi ni kikasetai ga tame
Kurushimu ageku no hate
Juu ji katame
Ima wo tanoshimitain da ne
Let’s Hip Pop!!
Here we, Here we Go!!

Hashagu FUROA no ue
Ataman naka yusa yusaburu

**Hey DJ shashare
yeah X 3 kibun joujou no
Nami ni notte hajike tobe FANKIINAI
Nomo urai X 3 minna de odore!
Hip-Pop PIIPOO
Asa made MIRAKURU Number

MIRAABOORU
SUMOOKU no nioi
Tokeru you na HAAMONII
Mi ni matotte odori akasu
Gamushara na mama de

*Repeat
**Repeat

This lyric was added by: jjnewyork87
	
	
Kanji Lyric
Kanji Kibun Jojo 	

Hey DJ　カマせ　yeah×3　気分上々↑↑の
針落とせ　音鳴らせ　パーリナイ
飲もう　ライ×3　みんなで踊れ!
Hip-Pop　ピーポー　かけてよミラクルNumber

Yo!こんな時代に分かち合うMUSIC
探したくて回す地球儀
グラつく不安定生活　それだからバランス重視
良いことばかりじゃないから「頑張れる!」
最悪な日にキック
再起動のボタン　クリック!
DJかけて!!　今　TRIP

シャレてるビートに乗って　感じる体揺らそうよ

Hey DJ　カマせ　yeah×3　気分上々↑↑の
針落とせ　音鳴らせ　パーリナイ
飲もう　ライ×3　みんなで踊れ!
Hip-Pop　ピーポー　かけてよミラクルNumber

Hip Hop, R&B, Pops Techno, House, Rock...
Hip Pop!!
オリジナル探すキーポイント
それぞれの色重ね合わすレインボー
君に聞かせたいが為　苦しむあげくの果て
十字固め
今を楽しみたいんだね
Let's Hip Pop!! Here we, Here we Go!!

はしゃぐフロアの上　頭ん中　ゆさゆさぶる

Hey DJ　シャシャれ　yeah×3　気分上々↑↑の
波に乗って　弾け飛べ　ファンキーナイ
飲もう　ライ×3　みんなで踊れ!
Hip-Pop　ピーポー　朝までミラクルNumber

ミラーボール　スモークのにおい
溶けるようなハーモニー
身にまとって踊り明かす　がむしゃらなままで

Hey DJ　カマせ　yeah×3　気分上々↑↑の
針落とせ　音鳴らせ　パーリナイ
飲もう　ライ×3　みんなで踊れ!
Hip-Pop　ピーポー　かけてよミラクルNumber

Hey DJ　シャシャれ　yeah×3　気分上々↑↑の
波に乗って　弾け飛べ　ファンキーナイ
飲もう　ライ×3　みんなで踊れ!
Hip-Pop　ピーポー　朝までミラクルNumber

This lyric was added by: aiiyka
	
	
Lyric Translation
Translation Kibun Jojo 	

Hey, DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah, feeling great
Drop the needle, make some noise, party night
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number

Yo! We can share our music in these times
Spinning the globe in search
Faltering in our unstable lives
That's why balance is important
It's not all good times, so "we can keep trying!"
Give that horrible day a kick
Press the restart button - click!
DJ, play it!! Now trip

Feel the stylish beat and rock your body

Hey, DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah, feeling great
Drop the needle, make some noise, party night
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number

Hip hop, R&B, pops, techno, house, rock...
Hip pop!!
The key point is searching for originality
Overlapping colors to make a rainbow
After all the suffering for wanting to ask you, in the end...
Cross hold
I wanna have fun now
Let's hip pop!! Here we, here we go!!

Playing on the floor, shaking your brain

Hey, DJ, keep it simple, yeah, yeah, yeah, feeling great
Ride the wave, bursting, jumping, funky night
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
Hip-pop people, miracle number all night long

Mirrorball, the smell of smoke
A harmony that'll make you melt
Wrap it around you and dance the night away recklessly

Hey, DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah, feeling great
Drop the needle, make some noise, party night
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number

Hey, DJ, keep it simple, yeah, yeah, yeah, feeling great
Ride the wave, bursting, jumping, funky night
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
Hip-pop people, miracle number all night long
